In the last video, we took a look at the mini-project that you worked on last lesson,
在上个视频中 我们对上节课的迷你项目进行了扩展
and extended it by deploying it.
即部署了该项目
Of course, we didn't do much with the deployed endpoint,
当然 我们没有怎么使用部署的端点
we just use it as another opportunity to test our model.
只是用它来测试模型
Now, we're going to start putting together all of the pieces
现在将一切都整合到一起
in order to make our endpoint work with the web app.
为了使网络应用能使用该端点
Remember that in the introduction,
在介绍的时候我提到
we talked about how we have two problems we need to overcome.
我们需要攻克两个问题
The first is that, our models endpoint expects to
第一个是模型端点要求输入是
receive a bag of words encoded version of the review.
用词袋表示的影评
However, our web app allows our user to
但是 网络应用允许用户
type any reviewing as a string. So, how do we do that?
以字符串的形式输入影评如何实现呢？
The second problem we have to overcome is one of security.
第二个问题是安全性
A diploid stage maker endpoint will only allow access to
部署的 StageMaker 端点仅允许
another object which is authenticated with
特定的对象访问 即向 AWS 验证身份
AWS and has permission to use a sage maker endpoint.
并且有权使用 StageMaker 端点的对象
That seems like overkill for a simple web app.
这对于简单的网络应用来说 似乎有点麻烦
So, what we'd like to do is create a new endpoint,
所以我们将新建一个端点
which is open to anyone,
任何人都可以访问该端点
that can receive a string as input,
它将接受字符串输入
perform some data processing,
对数据进行处理
and then send the process review off to our model,
然后将处理的影评发送给模型
get the result back,
获取结果
and return it to the original color.
并将结果返回给原始调用者
A nice picture to summarize this is right here.
这幅图表很好地总结了整个过程
So, we have our web app,
这是网络应用
and our web app takes a string from the user,
网络应用从用户那接受字符串
sends it off to the new end point that we're going to create,
将字符串发送给我们将创建的新端点
the new end point does some additional processing to
新端点对影评进行额外的处理
the review and then sends that process review over to the model.
然后将处理过的影评发送给模型
The model then creates a prediction,
模型做出预测
sends the prediction back to our newly created endpoint,
并将预测返回新创建的端点
and our endpoint returns the result back to our app,
端点将结果返回给应用
which it can then display to the user.
然后显示给用户
The technology we are going to use in order to implement
为了实现这个新端点
this new endpoint is first of all Lambda,
首先我们将使用 Lambda
and then we're going to create an interface to our Lambda function using API Gateway.
然后使用 API Gateway 针对 Lambda 函数创建一个接口
For now, let's just talk about lambda.
先介绍下 Lambda
Lambda is an example of something called a function as a service.
Lambda 属于函数即服务
That is, instead of having to create a server and have it running,
也就是说 与其创建一个服务器
the whole time, before you even need it,
并一直运行 甚至暂时还不需要用到该服务器
you can instead tell Amazon that you want
你可以告诉 Amazon
a specific function to be run whenever a specific event occurs.
每当发生特定的事件时 就运行特定的函数
That way, you don't have to pay for a server running the whole time,
这样的话 不用为一直运行的服务器付费
you only have to pay each time your function is run.
只需在每次函数运行时付费
Before setting up a lambda function though,
但是在设置 Lambda 函数之前
let's take a look at what kind of processing we need to do.
我们先看看需要怎么处理数据
To start with, our Lambda function is going to
首先 Lambda 函数将接收一个字符串
receive a string which contains a movie review.
其中包含影评
In our case, let's think of test review as
对我们来说 假设 test_review
being the string that will be sent to our Lambda function.
是将发送给 Lambda 函数的字符串
This is a rather negative review.
这条影评很负面
The first thing we need to do is to get rid of
首先需要删除
any HTML formatting that may appear inside of the string,
字符串中的所有 HTML 格式标记
and we need to remove any punctuation that appears.
以及所有的标点符号
If you recall from earlier,
之前
we wrote a function called review_to_words that did just
我们编写了一个函数 叫做 review_to_words()
that using only Python's built-in regular expression module.
它仅使用 Python 的内置正则表达式模块就可以删除标点和 HTML 标记
So, if we call this method on our sample review,
如果对示例影评调用此方法
and we print the result,
并输出结果
we will see that we get a cleaned up version of the review.
可以看到返回了清理后的影评
Next, we needed to create a bag of words encoding of the review.
接着 需要用词袋表示影评
To do that, we need a vocabulary which remember we
我们需要一个词汇表
constructed by looking at the most frequently occurring words in the training set.
我们之前通过查看训练集中最常出现的字词创建了词汇表
Based on this vocabulary,
下面我们将计算
we count the number of times each word in the vocabulary occurs in
词汇表中的每个字词出现在影评中的次数
our review and then we create a sequence that encodes all that information.
然后创建一个表示这一信息的序列
Doing that is pretty straightforward and in
这一步很简单
fact has been implemented in this method right here.
已经在这个方法中实现了
So, given our input which is the cleaned review,
传入输入（整洁的影评）
and vocabulary dictionary, the result is a bag of words encoded version of the review.
和词汇表字典后 结果是影评的词袋编码
Of course, if we were to just print this bag of words encoding out,
当然 如果输出这些词袋编码
it wouldn't make much sense.
看不出来是什么意思
Since it's just a vector of length equal to the size of the vocabulary.
因为它只是一个向量 长度等于词汇表的大小
As a sanity check though,
再次确认下
we can make sure that the bag of words encoded version of the review has
影评的词袋编码
the correct length and that agrees
长度是否正确
with the size of the vocabulary that we created earlier.
结果与之前创建的词汇表大小一致
Alright. So, what we'd like to do now is take our bag of words encoded
好的现在 我们将词袋格式的影评
review and send it off to our model to see what happens.
发送给模型 看看会发生什么
Of course, we shut down the endpoint of our model in the last video.
当然 我们在上个视频中关闭了端点
So, we need to start it back up again.
所以需要重新开启端点
Now, that our endpoint is up and running,
现在端点在运行了
we can send our bag of words encoded review off to it to see what happens.
我们可以将词袋格式的影评发送给它 看看会发生什么
Now, in the past,
之前
we have used the xgb predictor object in order to call our endpoint.
我们使用 xgb_predictor 对象调用端点
Of course, on the Lambda function we are going to create,
但是在要创建的 Lambda 函数中
we do not have access to this xgb predictor object.
我们无法访问这个 xgb_predictor 对象
So, we need to use the SageMaker interface itself.
所以需要使用 SageMaker 接口本身
To do that, we can get an object which points to the SageMaker runtime.
我们可以获取指向 sagemaker-runtime 的对象
Once we have that, using the name of
获取后
the endpoint we have created which we can remind ourselves here,
利用创建的端点的名称（可以在这里找到）...
we can use the invoke endpoint method making sure to include the name of the endpoint,
我们可以调用 invoke_endpoint 方法
the format of the data that we're sending it,
指定端点的名称 要发送的数据的格式
and the data itself.
以及数据本身
So, let's see what happens.
看看发生了什么
It seems we got an error.
似乎出现了错误
So, why did we get an error?
为何出错了？
Well, if we scroll down to the bottom,
向下滚动到底部
we can see that perimeter validation failed.
可以看到参数验证失败了
Which means that, some of the parameters that we
说明调用端点时
used to invoke our endpoint, were not correct.
用到的某些参数不正确
In particular, look at the value of the body.
看看 Body 的值
This doesn't look like a CSV file,
这看起来不像 CSV 文件
and we told SageMaker we're going to send a CSV file.
我们告诉 SageMaker 我们将发送 CSV 文件
Instead, we sent a list of integers.
但是我们发送的是整数列表
So, we need to make sure to serialize this object before we can
所以我们需要序列化此对象
properly call the invoke endpoint method. So, let's do that now.
然后才能正确地调用 invoke_endpoint 方法现在序列化该对象
Here, again, we include the name of the endpoint,
在这里 我们指定了端点的名称
we tell SageMaker the type of data that we will be including,
告诉 SageMaker 我们将发送的数据类型
and then, we serialize that data.
然后序列化该数据
We do that by joining together each of the entries in the bag of words vector,
方法是将词袋向量中的每个条目连接到一起
separating each of them by a comma.
用逗号分隔它们
Once we do this, we get a response,
调用该方法后 获得一个响应
and what does that response look like?
是什么样的响应？
A whole bunch of data.
是一堆数据
Of course, a lot of this data has to do with the fact that we communicate with
出现这些数据是因为
our model using an HTTP endpoint.
我们使用 HTTP 端点与模型通信
That is, an endpoint that is just a URL.
端点只是一个 URL
Looking right here though,
但是在这里
we can see that there's a body object and
可以看到 Body 对象
that body object contains the real information we're looking for.
这个 Body 对象包含我们要寻找的真正信息
So, what we can do is read in that body object
我们可以读入该 Body 对象
making sure to convert the result to a string, and what do we get?
记得将结果转换成字符串 准确率如何？
0.378.
0.378
It seems like our model did not think that review was particularly positive.
看来模型不认为这条影评是正面的
In fact, our model thought it was negative.
实际上 模型认为是负面的
So, this gives an example of the sort of processing we're
这就是我们要在
going to need to do inside of the Lambda function.
Lambda 函数中完成的处理过程
Next, we will actually set up the Lambda function.
接下来我们将设置 Lambda 函数